Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
34th Single Hit Keeper.
Double center is challenging to climb the highest staircase in Japan.
The rule is that you can't move on until you clear the mission in the middle of the stairs.
They aim to conquer 3333 steps and 10 missions!
Oh man, these two are such challenge-failure types, aren't they?
So far, they've failed to guess the names of all the songs in the first single mission.
400 more steps in total!
I was suddenly reminded of the severity of this prayer...
I wonder if Shiori would understand.
I'm sure she'd cry either way.
I'm sure I'll cry.
The two of them were able to match the place of their memories.
Kaki guessed Endo's favorite food in one shot.
After 1600 steps...
The fourth challenge is for the two of them to clock in at exactly 15 seconds!
Slow down, slow down.
Oh, wow.
That was fast.
Just a little over. Just a little over. Over and out with Thorlo.
I'm not coming back.
But he got the portrait Kaki drew on the second try right!
I wish I could give it to you, right?
Then the fifth challenge, jumping rope with two people, failed twice in a row!
We also failed at the 3-character silt tunnels with a different theme, and here alone, we went back and forth for a total of 600 more steps!
After getting stuck in the middle of the game three times in a row, we tried again with a different theme...
Guess the karaoke song of Kaki.
Mugs and sinks, here two of us tried several times to match the answers with our own unit songs.
Finally, we got out of the staircase loop and sang a bit of Saku-chan's part.
Thank you so much for the guesses!
And for the sixth mission, the members' silhouette kisses were answered just in time.
The seventh one was a test of luck... the challenge of alternately stabbing Blackbeard with the sword so that it wouldn't fly away was the last one...
You don't have to make it fly, you have it.
I have it. I have it.
You do?
That's a hell of an end.
I have it.
I've got it.
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it.
I don't know why it flies.
I've got it.
For the challenge of leaving only 340 500-milliliter bottles of water
In the challenge of leaving only 340
I reduced the water by one time each and weighed it...
Wow.
I exceeded...
3080.
I don't think so.
Where was 100 steps earlier?
Another 100 steps back in a row.
It's getting mentally tough.
Thank you.
You know...
You think while you climb, don't you?
Thank you very much.
The best in Japan.
I'm getting tired.
It's tough.
Tough.
No, no, no, it's okay to be tough.
If you're not strict, you can't grow.
That's great.
For some reason, the two of you are so positive.
Facing the challenge without complaining
The seventh mission, our third attempt
We succeeded in putting them in the trash at the same time.
Only two letters.
The eighth mission
Find the surnames of the Nokusaka members from the 50 syllables of hiragana.
Tsutsuki
There was a "e," and there was a "de," and there was a "de," and there was a "de
There, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there, there
Tsutsu
at last
Finally.
It is finished.
Tsugi
Funny!
I was one person short and had to go back 100 steps again.
Second attempt
We're up to four players again.
Sato's better?
Come on, somebody.
You want to go with Sato?
I prefer Sato.
We're running out of time.
But who's available?
Someone's not coming.
Oh, what?
I prefer Sato.
What?
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Got it!
We made it!
We did it!
Sato's better.
Kaki changed the members at the last minute
We've got five names.
We did it!
No, me.
I wonder if there are any other possibilities.
This is fun.
You can still get to the finish line with Endo persimmons.
What? Really?
That's what I was expecting.
Oh, no.
You were gone in an instant.
You climbed 2500 grams.
And on the way to the next challenge
I ran into Endo's second center station.
Go figure.
Here's Finger's Kloster on this day.
I feel amazingly weird.
It's cool, isn't it, Saku-chan?
Really?
Fingers crossed.
This time there's one Nogizaka CD on each of the 100 steps.
The two of you have traced the history of 33 CDs
Can they take the 34th step at the goal?
Oh, I got it.
It wasn't a little sudden, was it?
Eh, I know.
Compared to the first.
But you're fine.
I can't get my legs up anymore.
I know, right?
And the ninth challenge is
Measure the distance between the two of you to be exactly 3 meters and 40 centimeters.
How long?
I don't know.
I'm 15 centimeters from here to here.
I can't do it.
Okay, so...
So, if I go like this...
I can do it?
But then I realized that we're both a little bit taller than we should be, plus a little bit more.
So I made the cord a little longer than the distance between our outstretched arms.
That's it.
We can measure the distance between the two of us to be exactly 3m40cm.
We've got it!
There is only one challenge left
This challenge is one of the toughest ever, and it's not going to be easy.
Double center to overcome the challenge
Deepening that bond, the goal is finally approaching!
3000m zan here we come!
Two more to go!
Likes rock, baby!
I'm here.
I don't think we should go back here.
We're going below 3000 meters.
Let's go for it.
I don't want to go back this far.
Last one we drew was...
Revenge Challenge.
You can take on the most confident mission you've ever failed.
I chose the three-letter word Shiritori
I don't know if I can finish here.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Start with a tree.
A tree
Looks
Eyes...
Crow
Violets
Le
Renge
Ge
Hu
Either one
fusuma
pillow
trumpet
pants
smiki
ki
kittako
sea otter (Enhydra lutris)
sea otter
carp
Carp
Failed again on the 10th mission
The last wall.
Can the two of us make it through?
Then...
It's so bright
I think it's the sunset.
No, you're right.
Are you okay?
I think the light just turned a little sideways.
Can we go home? I don't know if I can go home.
My feet are killing me.
We're running out of time to go home.
I'm going to try again... for one last mission.
Okay.
Double-centered single CD dominoes!
All the single CDs we've collected so far
on the dominoes.
And don't stop.
If you can eat them all clean...
It's clear!
The 30 CDs collected so far
30 CDs.
It's going to take me a minute and a half to line them all up.
I don't know how we're going to beat it.
There's an opening.
How are we gonna do that?
Put one down.
Sakka, put down another one.
I'll put it down, put it down, put it down.
Okay.
Less than a minute and a half.
Wait a minute.
It's going down.
Oh, Celeb.
This is surprisingly flat on the bottom.
It's probably the two of you who have been lining up cd's smoothly from the beginning without knocking any of them over
Surprisingly far.
Not too far.
I see... the order is good.
But when it's far away...
But I'm a little scared.
I'm a little scared, so I'm going to fill in the gaps.
I don't know.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
It's okay.
That was good.
That's good.
Now if we can just get it down nice.
You can do it... you can do it.
There's a little bit of a push this time.
Just give me a little pause.
I'm gonna put it down.
All right, you're good to go.
I can do it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it. I got it.
Seino.
Double-centered kizuna dominoes.
Will the last challenge succeed?
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
I've got it.
Oh, that's good.
I don't want you to fail again.
Ready?
I got it.
Good, good, good.
That's good.
That's it.
It went down nice and clean.
Sorry about that.
We've completed the entire mission.
Now it's up to the two of us to collect all of Nogizaka's steps and get to the finish line.
If I had to do it alone...
I'd be in hell.
That was fun.
Here we go!
All we have to do now is climb.
Twenty-three hundred.
My legs are killing me!
200th step.
Two hundred.
Okay.
Here we go.
How many times do we dream?
I like number two.
We're the same.
Nogizaka's songs...
The second number is really good.
I like number 2 in Monopoly too.
The second number.
Sabi
Nobody wakes up from a dream but...
"Let's go back to sleep.
I love you
I like the beginning of the second verse
But it's true that I'm alive right here, right now.
We're all alive.
We all think differently, but we're all alive.
Here we go.
Okay, 3,300.
Three hundred and thirty-three thousand yen.
Ohkorisama heaven.
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
Everything we've seen so far has been picked up.
Finally, the two of us have traced all of Nogizaka's history so far.
Only 33 bullets left. At the top of the mountain, we take the 34th new step.
Ah!
We beat the summit.
What's that? I see it.
The stone steps are 3,330 meters high, like a white dragon climbing a mountain.
33 is the highest in Japan!
Wow, here it comes!
Here it comes!
There's a tiny staircase over there!
Why do you guys have stairs?
It's not good.
Right foot.
Ready?
Here we go!
Here they come!
We're up!
We made it!
3330 meters.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We made it!
Wow.
That's amazing.
I'm amazed you made it!
Finally, we're going to a certain temple of Mr. Yui
I'm going to make a written request.
The temple is that way.
That way.
Oh, what does it say?
Fishing temple
It was still 1000m
1km
So for the written request
I have to go to the temple for another 30 minutes.
I have to go to the fishing temple.
I walked.
Why did you walk?
I wanted to make it to 3333.
What the hell?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
And finally, two double-centered hit kigas.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Three, two, one, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ooh.
Oh!
Ooh!
34th single
May it be a big hit for Monopoly!
It's coming!
Great success!
So pray for our 34th single to be a big hit!
Yay!
You won't give me this!
You don't complain at all!
Positive attitude.
How's it going?
I was tired, but Saki was there, so we talked while we climbed.
That was the best part.
How's it going, Endo?
I'm almost dragging you down.
You're right.
You didn't notice when you were doing it?
I did, but looking at it again...
Blackbeard was amazing.
Genius.
That was more like a clear shot.
That's where you're supposed to put it.
I got it.
Wasn't his leg tough?
Yeah, they were.
That's why you couldn't jump rope.
That's not true.
Definitely not.
That's the difference.
He's all baton...
He's cute and all, but...
I'm sure you're exhausted... at the end.
Thighs.
I can't get my legs up around my thighs anymore.
No, of course not.
But Kakki was there, so we were talking while we climbed, which made it easier.
I love the lyrics of the second last verse!
It doesn't sound like Endo.
Also, there's a single for every 100 steps, so you can look back.
That's good, too.
And the 34th one is just right.
It's really, really good.
And the fact that the two of them weren't born yet...
They weren't born yet, right?
They weren't born.
They weren't born yet.
How was it?
I can understand if they met as friends and had their pick of partners.
But if they met as business associates and could create such a wonderful, gentle atmosphere... it's really relaxing to watch.
And since the group has been in a really good mood since they started their activities.
I feel like the two of you are at peace.
I feel that we have to create such an environment for them to be able to work in peace.
I feel that there are really two beautiful people in this group.
It's true that they don't complain at all.
But if it were other members, they would complain a lot.
No, I think they would.
And the second time they dance, I'm like, "Are you serious?
Can I use that hand?
You'd say it, right, like Iwamoto?
I'm sure she won't.
She'll say, "You don't use it.
I'll do it.
You will?
I did it.
I don't know.
But the two of you have been working really hard this season.
Especially since you're in the center, you've been working hard.
And our schedule is really tight at the end of the year to pray for a hit.
And the two who are working the hardest are doing such a great job.
It would be crazy if they don't sell well.
That's right.
Tsutsui drew a portrait of me, too.
I'm so glad.
I'm backstage there.
I know, the stairs here are tough, too.
The stairs here are tough, too.
You're on the third floor, right?
That's right.
We're on the second floor.
I always feel that way.
And yet there's a calm atmosphere all the way through.
Even Tsutsui sees it, it's calm.
It's extremely calm.
I think Tsutsui is the calmest.
I see.
Tsutsui is calm, but inside he's different.
I'm happy, happy, happy.
Happy, happy, happy.
Laughter
laughter
But I think it's true that the two of you have this kind of ha-ha-ha-ha feeling, and I think to a certain extent Kaki is kind of pulling you along, you know.
Kaki is kind of leading the way to a certain extent.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but Endo, compared to the past, he talks a lot quicker.
He used to be like cotton wool.
He's got a stag on his back.
You've been like this for a long time.
He's been like this for a long time.
I know, I know.
That's pretty much it.
Two sides are getting more solid.
I thought for sure one of them would cry.
You don't even cry.
I know it was hard for you, but...
I'm glad we got to see the bond between the two of them during the game.
I think it was only possible because it was the two of them.
I was really talking to Mr. Himura about this.
I wish you could have made the last mission go back to the start.
Then I wouldn't have said it.
You two don't get mad?
I've never seen you angry, Saku-chan.
That's great!
I'm not angry.
It's like there's no "Do's" in anger or sorrow.
Like Gandhi.
Reincarnation.
Reincarnation of Gandhi
After this, a big event will happen.
Now, let's pray for a hit version of Monopoly!
Idol shampoo.
How cute!
And there's a kid in the back.
Oh, my God.
Try it.
Scary, scary, scary.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
The bear I've been waiting to see.
Penck beckons.
He's so cute.
Here we go.
I love this.
I know what you mean.
There it is.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Watch out.
Speaking of likely winners...
I'll match it.
Match?
All right.
I'm in.
I'm sure of it.
100!
100th step.
Boom of the sun
Wow!
How did you do that?
I'm so bad at this.
Like this.
He's waiting for you.
Beautiful is the belly.
Yes, beautiful.
It's getting heavier and heavier.
My muscles must be sore.
I'll see you tomorrow.
My muscles won't be sore in a day.
Good luck.
Thanks for your hard work.
That side is bigger.
A little bit.
I have to walk here.
Goodbye, Easleeter.
Easleeter.
Is it bad?
It's too bright.
Ooh.
I can do it today because I can do it someday
Singulonicity.
Selfish.
Yeah!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
I can do it here, I can do it there.
On the way back, I want to take the long way around.
Fingered
Flowers and birds.
Yes.
Happy protective colors.
Boca bocosteinal.
Yay!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, wow!
Oh, wow.
It's a Fingard cluster.
There are many stones
Himegawa...
Akucheri.
Oh, here comes Zundon!
Is this still last summer?
Yes, it is.
I see.
You can pick one.
Yeah.
That's great.
All of it.
Thirty-one.
How many steps?
You're on your own.
Seino
Airey
I'm here!
I'm up!
You couldn't do the three-letter word game? Why can't you do it?
I think I can do that one in a heartbeat.
Try it.
No, no, no, it's okay. We can do it here.
You can do it.
You can do it. You can do it.
That was hard.
Okay, give me the first one.
I guess you can do it with or without the muddled dot.
Ane, I did it.
That's okay, too.
I'm serious.
It'll be so clear it won't matter.
Really?
Yeah, you can probably do it.
I'm sure we can do it.
Then Monopoly, too.
Can I have a Monopoly game?
Okay, let's get started.
MOMO.
What?
Quickly.
Do it once, do it once.
There it is, the natural one.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, can we do without it for one more time?
There it is.
I'm in too much of a hurry.
Yui...
Go for it!
A little bit onyan.
Yes!
Let's go!
Here we go!
Glue!
LOL!
Oh, look out!
It's back again!
I can't do it!
I can't!
You're already trying to tell me imoji, already.
LOL.
I'm more nervous than I thought I'd be when I was about to do it.
I don't want to go back 100 steps.
It might be tougher than usual.
Might be tougher.
Next time, we'll have a big year-end party to celebrate all the hard work we've done this year.
The 3rd, 4th, and 5th wards each want to get together and do it.
The last of the year 2023, somehow we're closing with a synchronized party filled with laughter and tears.
Extension!
You did it, didn't you?
What? What?
Are you alone?
You've got to be kidding me.
The latest Blue Leo from Kakitamura and Endo Tsukui.
Endo Tsukui and Kakitamura have released two sheets at the same time, both filled with paper shells carefully selected by the two of them!
2 shells are also included with a large increase in the number of shells and of course the two's unhappiness!
Get it on January 17!
Hello, I'm Runo Nakamura, I've been into apples lately and I have a lot of them at home!
Please subscribe to my channel, and good bye!